<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<metadata xml:lang="en"><Esri><CreaDate>20120821</CreaDate><CreaTime>17115500</CreaTime><ArcGISFormat>1.0</ArcGISFormat><ArcGISstyle>North American Profile of ISO19115 2003</ArcGISstyle><SyncOnce>TRUE</SyncOnce><ArcGISProfile>NAP</ArcGISProfile><DataProperties><itemProps><itemLocation><linkage Sync="TRUE">file://\\HARNEY\C$\MGIS6\mgisdata\Metadata\REGIS_Org_Template</linkage><protocol Sync="TRUE">Local Area Network</protocol></itemLocation></itemProps><copyHistory><copy source="C:\gisclass\mgisdata\Metadata\REGIS_Org_Template" dest="\\HARNEY\C$\MGIS6\mgisdata\Metadata\REGIS_Org_Template" date="20120821" time="17115500"/></copyHistory></DataProperties><scaleRange><minScale>150000000</minScale><maxScale>5000</maxScale></scaleRange></Esri><dataIdInfo><idStatus><ProgCd value="001"/></idStatus><idCitation><editorTitleExpand>False</editorTitleExpand><citRespParty xmlns=""><rpIndName>GIS Project Coordinator</rpIndName><rpOrgName>Re-GIS, Inc.</rpOrgName><rpCntInfo xmlns=""><cntAddress addressType="both"><delPoint>2467 Elven Way</delPoint><city>Rivendell</city><adminArea>ME</adminArea><postCode>12345</postCode><country>US</country><eMailAdd>gisdept@regis.com</eMailAdd></cntAddress><cntPhone><voiceNum tddtty="">555-217-2056</voiceNum><faxNum>555-217-2001</faxNum></cntPhone><cntHours>0800 to 1700 EST/EST</cntHours></rpCntInfo><rpPosName>GIS Project Coordinator</rpPosName><role><RoleCd value="006"/></role><displayName>New ReGIS Contact</displayName></citRespParty></idCitation><resConst><Consts xmlns=""><useLimit>&lt;DIV STYLE="text-align:Left;"&gt;&lt;DIV&gt;&lt;DIV&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The data were developed by REGIS, Inc. for the use of its clients and affiliates as established by contract. As used herein, "Geodata" shall mean any digital data set consisting of geographic data coordinates and associated attributes. "Client" is the person or organization who has contracted with REGIS specifically for the development of the Geodata covered by this statement. "User" is any entity, including the Client, who displays, prints, plots, copies, or utilizes the data in any way. The redistribution rights for this data set: Redistribution rights are granted by REGIS for hard-copy renditions or static, electronic map images (e.g. .gif, .jpeg, etc.) that are plotted, printed, or publicly displayed by Users with proper metadata and source/copyright attribution to REGIS, provided such use is allowed by the Client. Geodata provided to Clients as part of a contract with REGIS may be redistributed by the Client with proper metadata and source/copyright attribution to REGIS. The terms and conditions below apply to all the data sets provided to Clients and Users by REGIS. Proprietary Rights and Copyright: The User acknowledges that the Data and Related Materials contain proprietary and confidential property of REGIS and its Client(s). The Data and Related Materials are owned by REGIS and its Client(s) and are protected by United States copyright laws and applicable international copyright treaties and/or conventions. Limited Warranty and Disclaimer: REGIS warrants that the media upon which the Data and Related Materials are provided will be free from defects in materials and workmanship under normal use and service for a period of ninety (90) days from the date of receipt. In the event that the Client(s) choose to redistribute the Geodata, please use proper proprietary or copyright attribution for the various data source(s), and provide the associated metadata file(s) with the Geodata. In compliance with metadata standards, REGIS has attempted to practice proper metadata methodologies by providing any data source information, descriptions, and file names to assist in this effort.&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</useLimit></Consts><LegConsts xmlns=""><useLimit>THE DATA AND RELATED MATERIALS ARE EXCLUDED FROM THE LIMITED WARRANTY, AND THE CLIENT OR USER EXPRESSLY ACKNOWLEDGE THAT THE DATA CONTAINS SOME NONCONFORMITIES, DEFECTS, OR ERRORS. REGIS DOES NOT WARRANT THAT THE DATA WILL MEET USERS'S NEEDS OR EXPECTATIONS; THAT THE USE OF THE DATA WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED; OR THAT ALL NONCONFORMITIES, DEFECTS, OR ERRORS CAN OR WILL BE CORRECTED. THE USER SHOULD ALWAYS VERIFY ACTUAL DATA. SHOULD THE CLIENT IDENTIFY NONCONFORMITIES, DEFECTS, OR ERRORS IN THE DATA DURING THE PERIOD OF WORK COVERED BY THE CONTRACT AND REPORT THEM IN WRITING TO REGIS, REGIS WILL ATTEMPT TO CORRECT THEM SUBJECT TO TIME AND BUDGET CONSTRAINTS IMPOSED UPON THE PROJECT, OR PROVIDE THE CLIENT WITH WRITTEN NOTICE THAT SUCH NONCONFORMITIES, DEFECTS, OR ERRORS CANNOT BE CORRECTED. TIME AND RESOURCES PROVIDED BY REGIS TO MAKE CORRECTIONS ARE CHARGABLE TO THE PROJECT CONTRACT AS ARE ALL OTHER SERVICES PROVIDED BY REGIS. IN NO EVENT IS REGIS OBLIGATED TO CORRECT NONCONFORMITIES, DEFECTS, OR ERRORS ONCE THE CONTRACT PERIOD WITH THE CLIENT HAS EXPIRED. EXCEPT FOR THE LIMITED WARRANTY SET FORTH ABOVE, THE DATA AND RELATED MATERIALS CONTAINED THEREIN ARE PROVIDED "AS-IS," WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. HIGH RISK ACTIVITIES: (A) THE DATA AND RELATED MATERIALS ARE NOT FAULT-TOLERANT AND ARE NOT DESIGNED, MANUFACTURED, OR INTENDED FOR USE OR RESALE FOR INSURANCE UNDERWRITING OR WITH CRITICAL HEALTH AND SAFETY OR ONLINE CONTROL EQUIPMENT IN HAZARDOUS ENVIRONMENTS THAT REQUIRE FAIL-SAFE PERFORMANCE, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE OPERATION OF NUCLEAR FACILITIES, NAVIGATION OR GUIDANCE (I.E., AIRCRAFT, NAUTICAL VEHICLE, ETC.), OR COMMUNICATION SYSTEMS, AIR TRAFFIC CONTROL, EMERGENCY RESPONSE, TERRORISM PREVENTION OR RESPONSE, LIFE SUPPORT, OR WEAPONS SYSTEMS ("HIGH RISK ACTIVITIES"). REGIS SPECIFICALLY DISCLAIMS ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTY OF FITNESS FOR HIGH RISK ACTIVITIES. (B) TO THE EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, THE USER AGREES TO INDEMNIFY, DEFEND, AND HOLD REGIS, ITS OFFICERS, DIRECTORS, EMPLOYEES, AGENTS, SUBCONTRACTORS, CLIENTS, SUCCESSORS, AND ASSIGNS HARMLESS FROM AND AGAINST ANY AND ALL LIABILITY, LOSSES, CLAIMS, EXPENSES (INCLUDING ATTORNEYS' FEES), DEMANDS, OR DAMAGES OF ANY KIND, INCLUDING DIRECT, INDIRECT, SPECIAL, PUNITIVE, INCIDENTAL, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, ARISING OUT OF OR IN ANY WAY CONNECTED WITH CLIENT'S USE OR PERMITTING THE USE BY OTHERS OF THE DATA, AND VENDOR'S HARDWARE OR SOFTWARE FOR HIGH RISK ACTIVITIES. DELIVERY OF THE DATA, AND VENDOR'S HARDWARE OR SOFTWARE DOES NOT CONSTITUTE A WAIVER OF THE RIGHTS AND OBLIGATIONS SET FORTH IN THIS ARTICLE. IN NO EVENT SHALL REGIS AND/OR ITS CLIENT(S) BE LIABLE FOR COSTS OF PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES; LOST PROFITS, LOST SALES, OR BUSINESS EXPENDITURES, INVESTMENTS, OR COMMITMENTS IN CONNECTION WITH ANY BUSINESS; LOSS OF ANY GOODWILL; OR FOR ANY INDIRECT, SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES ARISING OUT OF THIS AGREEMENT OR USE OF THE DATA AND RELATED MATERIALS, HOWEVER CAUSED, ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, AND WHETHER OR NOT REGIS OR ITS CLIENTS(S) HAVE BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE. THESE LIMITATIONS SHALL APPLY NOTWITHSTANDING ANY FAILURE OF ESSENTIAL PURPOSE OF ANY EXCLUSIVE REMEDY. </useLimit></LegConsts></resConst><dataChar><CharSetCd value="004"/></dataChar><idPoC xmlns=""><rpIndName>GIS Project Coordinator</rpIndName><rpOrgName>Re-GIS, Inc.</rpOrgName><rpCntInfo xmlns=""><cntAddress addressType="both"><delPoint>2467 Elven Way</delPoint><city>Rivendell</city><adminArea>ME</adminArea><postCode>12345</postCode><country>US</country><eMailAdd>gisdept@regis.com</eMailAdd></cntAddress><cntPhone><voiceNum tddtty="">555-217-2056</voiceNum><faxNum>555-217-2001</faxNum></cntPhone><cntHours>0800 to 1700 EST/EST</cntHours></rpCntInfo><rpPosName>GIS Project Coordinator</rpPosName><role><RoleCd value="006"/></role><displayName>New ReGIS Contact</displayName><displayName>GIS Project Coordinator</displayName></idPoC><resMaint xmlns=""><maintCont xmlns=""><rpIndName>GIS Project Coordinator</rpIndName><rpOrgName>Re-GIS, Inc.</rpOrgName><rpCntInfo><cntAddress addressType="both"><delPoint>2467 Elven Way</delPoint><city>Rivendell</city><adminArea>ME</adminArea><postCode>12345</postCode><country>US</country><eMailAdd>gisdept@regis.com</eMailAdd></cntAddress><cntPhone><voiceNum tddtty="">555-217-2056</voiceNum><faxNum>555-217-2001</faxNum></cntPhone><cntHours>0800 to 1700 EST/EST</cntHours></rpCntInfo><rpPosName>GIS Project Coordinator</rpPosName><role><RoleCd value="006"/></role><displayName>New ReGIS Contact</displayName><displayName>GIS Project Coordinator</displayName></maintCont></resMaint></dataIdInfo><mdHrLv><ScopeCd value="006"/></mdHrLv><mdConst><Consts xmlns=""><useLimit>No use constraints on metadata.</useLimit></Consts><LegConsts xmlns=""><useLimit>Use metadata at your own risk.  No guarantee is made as to completeness or accuracy of the metadata.</useLimit></LegConsts><SecConsts xmlns=""><useLimit>No security constraints on this metadata.</useLimit></SecConsts></mdConst><mdMaint xmlns=""><maintFreq><MaintFreqCd value="011"/></maintFreq><maintScp><ScopeCd value="005"/></maintScp><maintCont xmlns=""><rpIndName>GIS Project Coordinator</rpIndName><rpOrgName>Re-GIS, Inc.</rpOrgName><rpCntInfo><cntAddress addressType="both"><delPoint>2467 Elven Way</delPoint><city>Rivendell</city><adminArea>ME</adminArea><postCode>12345</postCode><country>US</country><eMailAdd>gisdept@regis.com</eMailAdd></cntAddress><cntPhone><voiceNum tddtty="">555-217-2056</voiceNum><faxNum>555-217-2001</faxNum></cntPhone><cntHours>0800 to 1700 EST/EST</cntHours></rpCntInfo><rpPosName>GIS Project Coordinator</rpPosName><role><RoleCd value="006"/></role><displayName>New ReGIS Contact</displayName><displayName>GIS Project Coordinator</displayName></maintCont></mdMaint><mdContact xmlns=""><rpIndName>GIS Project Coordinator</rpIndName><rpOrgName>Re-GIS, Inc.</rpOrgName><rpCntInfo xmlns=""><cntAddress addressType="both"><delPoint>2467 Elven Way</delPoint><city>Rivendell</city><adminArea>ME</adminArea><postCode>12345</postCode><country>US</country><eMailAdd>gisdept@regis.com</eMailAdd></cntAddress><cntPhone><voiceNum tddtty="">555-217-2056</voiceNum><faxNum>555-217-2001</faxNum></cntPhone><cntHours>0800 to 1700 EST/EST</cntHours></rpCntInfo><rpPosName>GIS Project Coordinator</rpPosName><role><RoleCd value="006"/></role><displayName>New ReGIS Contact</displayName><displayName>GIS Project Coordinator</displayName></mdContact><distInfo xmlns=""><distributor xmlns=""><distorCont xmlns=""><rpIndName>Re-GIS Webmaster</rpIndName><rpOrgName>Re-GIS, Inc.</rpOrgName><rpCntInfo xmlns=""><cntAddress addressType="both"><delPoint>2467 Elven Way</delPoint><city>Rivendell</city><adminArea>ME</adminArea><postCode>12345</postCode><country>US</country><eMailAdd>webmaster@regis.com</eMailAdd></cntAddress><cntPhone><voiceNum tddtty="">555-217-2056</voiceNum><faxNum>555-217-2001</faxNum></cntPhone><cntHours>0800 to 1700 EST/EST</cntHours></rpCntInfo><rpPosName>ITS Web Designer</rpPosName><role><RoleCd value="005"/></role><displayName>New ReGIS Contact</displayName><editorSave>False</editorSave><displayName>GIS Project Coordinator</displayName></distorCont></distributor></distInfo></metadata>
